Simon, Carleton; Papers apap073
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Memorabilia, 1882-1889; 1884-1896; 1902; 1907; 1917-1950; 7; 3 in.
  - Rosters of the New York State Association of Chiefs of Police, 1949-1950 (Box 3 (7-Memorabilia), Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook, 1885-1889 (Box 3 (7-Memorabilia), Folder 24)
  - Skull X-ray, 1935 (Box 3 (7-Memorabilia), Folder 25)
  - Wallet, 1917-1950 (Box 3 (7-Memorabilia), Folder 26)
- Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work, 1900; 1906; 1921-1935; 1939; 1949; 8; 1 in.
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  Published articles about Carleton Simon's work as a criminologist and his views on crime.
  - The Conqueror, 1924 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 27)
  - Gunning for Drug Smugglers, 1921 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 28)
  - Have You a Wrong Way Brain?, 1939 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 29)
  - How They'll Catch Tomorrow's Kidnapers, 1935 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 30)
  - News Release About Young Criminals, ca. 1949 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 31)
  - Occupations in Relation to Health: The Physician, 1906 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 32)
  - Phonograph of Dr. Carleton Simon, 1900 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 33)
  - Sherlock Holmes Up to Date, 1935 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 34)
  - "Try Anything Once?"--Don't!, 1923 (Box 3 (8-Publications About Carleton Simon and His Work.), Folder 35)